Hi everyone. And yeah, thanks for being
here.
Let's just dive right in. Today's
session that I'm going to be giving to
you is modernizing systems observability
with AI and LLMs.
As mentioned already, my name is Jason
Hand. I am a senior developer advocate
at Datadog, primarily focusing on topics
such as SRE, site reliability
engineering, DevOps, and as we'll see
today, artificial intelligence is of
course the new hotness that everybody's
talking about, and Datadog is no
different.
So, before we get too far along into our
sessions though, I wanted to provide
this link for you because I've done a
ton of research to provide some
information for you today that is real
just great resources to have on hand.
You can also go get the slides. Pretty
much everything I'm going to be sharing
today is available at this link. It's
just a GitHub repo.
So, feel free to go visit that after now
if you'd like. I'll definitely give you
these links this link again later in the
session, so don't worry if you don't
capture that now. I just know a lot of
you like to have that up front.
Okay, so getting started here, I thought
we would first off just have a little
thought experiment and have you ever
really given much thought to how much
data is being generated annually on a
global scale? I know that that's
something I haven't really given much
thought about here until until recently,
but according to some of the
the data that I found as I, you know,
began researching this stuff, it looks
like since around 2010, the volume of
the data that's been generated each year
has grown steadily. I don't think
anybody's all that surprised by that at
all. But what is surprised made me is or
surprising is that about 90% of the
world's data has been produced in just
the past 2 years. So, in other words,
since 2010, so like 14 years or so,
that figure has skyrocketed from around
2 ZB
all the way up to a little over 150 or
just under 150 ZB as of 2024,
which is crazy. And for those of you who
aren't sure, I had never heard of a ZB
until recently when I was looking into
this stuff. I can't believe this is the
size we're at. And to give you some
context, a petabyte, most of us are
probably familiar with with petabytes.
That's 1 million GB.
An exabyte is 1,000 petabytes, and a ZB
is 1,000 exabytes. So, we're talking
massive, massive amounts of data. Kind
of to Deion's point earlier is that we
just are swimming in data. There's just
so much of it. And really, there's no
sign of it slowing down at all. The
trend is still moving upwards, of
course. Really not a surprise with
global data generated generation
projected to be
or projected to increase rather by about
150% by 2025,
reaching probably over 180 ZB.
And you can see here in this quote that
I pulled, a lot of that data is actually
real-time data that's created by
connected users having digital
interactions pretty much all day long.
Another
infographic that I came across that I
wanted to share with you that I thought
was really interesting when it comes to
data. This one here shows that every
minute of every day, people are sending
somewhere around 241 million emails.
Viewers are watching over 43 years of
streaming content. WhatsApp users are
sending messages somewhere around 41.6
million of them a day
or every minute of every day. Fans of
Taylor Swift are streaming her songs
69,000 times per day or per minute per
day. And the average person is producing
about 102 megabytes. Now, these numbers,
some of them are pretty staggering, some
of them are probably not all that
surprising, but the point is that we're
just dealing with massive massive
amounts of data these days.
Um and the thing is I think that a lot
of us uh
have started to realize is there's a lot
of answers in that data. A lot of the
questions that we have as developers, as
operations folks,
um even as businesses, there's a lot of
things that we can uncover in that data
and making sense of that large volume,
that vast amount of data that we have
now is sort of the goal of a lot of the
things that we're going to be talking
about today.
Now, you might be thinking to yourself,
well, that's interesting. Those are neat
statistics and numbers, but that's not
my data. That's not the kind of data
that I deal with on a day-to-day basis.
I'm dealing with uh things that are much
different than that. Um you're probably
dealing with platform generated data,
right? You're probably thinking, well,
that's that the stuff I'm interested in
uh especially from an observability
point of view is really something that's
related to our system or maybe to the
applications that are running within our
platform or our systems. There's a lot
of generated data that is being um
well, generated that we need to make
sense of. And some of that is coming
from our servers or other servers other
people's servers, maybe it's coming from
cloud, from infrastructure and services
that are running up in the cloud. It
could be coming from your users just as
they interact with your systems. And of
course, when things go wrong, there's
data that's generated there as well.
A research report by Tech Strong
uh research found that about 63%
of companies that they uh surveyed plan
to make investments in observability
over the next 2 years with about 21%
saying that's going to be quote
significant
uh in the in that time. So, you can see
that this is something now just in terms
of the data and understanding that from
an observability perspective is becoming
a high priority for a lot of
organizations.
In a different report, the AI-augmented
DevOps survey report from TechStrong,
they found there that about 46% of the
respondents were working for
organizations that plan to adopt AI to
help augment their DevOps teams over the
next year or so.
And you know, with only about 20% of
those respondents actually saying they
have no plan whatsoever.
So, I thought what we would do is
actually understand in what ways are
those organizations planning to adopt AI
tools to augment their DevOps and
observability efforts over the next 12
months.
Well, a lot of it has to do with kind of
like two bucketed groups that I've come
up with. You can kind of think of it as
four, I guess, with development and
testing being two of them, and then
operations and monitoring being the
other bucket. Probably most of us on
this session are
identifying with one of these, you know,
in terms of the things that we do in our
day-to-day with our primary focus. So,
these are the areas that that I think
are the most interesting to talk about
the expected benefits. And then when I
say expected benefits, what I mean is
that we're so early along in a lot of
this is that we haven't really realized
some of the benefits. There are
organizations out there and teams that
have been experimenting with AI and LLMs
in their observability practices for a
while now, or just AI in general within
their organizations, and we've got data
that we can
share about that. And in fact,
the link I have here at the bottom of
the slide will lead you to the results
of the of those surveys that we talked
about, where you can see they do measure
a notable increase in productivity. I'm
going to come back to productivity here
in a moment because there's a there's a
few ways for us to break that down.
But they're also seeing a reduction in
the skills gap as an expected benefit
from a lot of just AI in in sort of
DevOps teams in general. And the same
with improving the quality of their
software as well as lowering their
operational costs. So, these are the
ways that um, you know, organizations
are expecting to find some benefit by
going down this path of leveraging AI
and LLM enabled platforms for their
observability efforts, or really just
their DevOps efforts in general. But, if
we back up and take a little little
closer look at the increase in
productivity, we can break this down
into a couple of categories as well. The
first one being code development. I
think a lot of us has probably played
with the variety of different co-pilots
that are out there, whether that's
GitHub co-pilot, or ChatGPT, or Claude,
Sonic. Whatever the case may be, there's
a lot of AI enabled tools out there that
are really speeding up and helping us
with code development. They're helping
improve the quality of the writing of
the code. They're helping us with
debugging it and making sure that it's,
you know, at least a little bit freer of
the few fewer of defects, or has fewer
defects, I guess you could say.
Uh, also finding ways to do code reviews
in an automated way, and and reducing
the errors, uh, is a is another way that
they're seeing productivity gains. And
then the AI co-pilots really themselves
are helping write the the code faster,
or just helps us write code faster, and
understand the code and the structures
behind them a little bit easier. I know
for me personally, I don't write a ton
of code, but lately, over the past year
or so, as I've had situations where I
did need to write code, or I was working
on a project, these co-pilots and and
the different tools that are out there
now have really enhanced my abilities to
to put out some, you know, relatively
useful code. And uh, it's been uh, you
know, and I'm just one one person. I'm
not even writing code in in production
systems, so I think the increase in
productivity there is pretty clear. The
other category that we're seeing some,
uh, productivity increases too, is in
the testing and quality areas. And a lot
of that has to do with just efficiencies
now with the way that the stuff is being
tested, the code's being tested.
Improvements in also the test script
creation process. I think that's another
area we're seeing some uh increased
productivity. And the automated testing
uh and quality assurance processes in
general, being able to apply some AI
tooling and and
enhancements there. And then last, uh I
think all of us have probably read
marketing material or seen something
about how how AI is help is helping to
detect and auto heal and even predict uh
a lot of defects before they make it
into our production environments.
So, those are those are the expected
benefits that I I think a lot of
organizations have already seen or maybe
that they're expecting to see.
But, if we focus a little bit more down
to just the observability and not not
DevOps as a whole, but really just
focusing into this world of monitoring
and tracing and and all that kind of
stuff, the observability stuff is what
we're all here to learn about. And I
think the best place for us to examine
what's going on out there across the
industry is to take a look at the the
leaders in the space and the visionaries
in the space. And those those terms,
leaders and visionaries, that's coming
directly from Gartner and their magic
quadrant. I'm sure at this point all of
us have seen some version of a magic
quadrant. There's a lot of them out
there. This is a recent one that came
out that shows the magic quadrant for
observability platform. So, I figured
we'd start here in terms of exploring,
well, what is out there and what are
vendors providing? What what can we do?
So, we're going to focus just on these
here that I've highlighted, although I'm
not going to go into each of them
individually and tell you one by one
what all of them offer. I'm going to
give you a whole bunch of things that
just sort of sums up what all of those
vendors are offering, and then we'll
take a little closer look at it later.
The first one I think we've probably all
seen in a number of ways is anomaly
anomaly detection. This is something
that a lot of vendors, a lot of tools
have had available for quite some time.
DataDog has something called Watchdog,
which falls into this category. It's
really a a learning powered tool that
really helps us spot unusual patterns
and system behavior from the logs and
just different areas of the system of
the data that's coming into the system
looking for those patterns that might be
easily missed on a by human.
Another area is in root cause analysis.
I don't love the term root cause but I
understand the process. It's you know in
in least in this case where we're
talking about AI enabled driven AI
enabled RCAs. It's helping us understand
those underlying issues and correlate
things and and be able to streamline the
incident understanding and resolution
process.
Another area is predictive analytics. We
see that across a lot of the vendors
trying to provide some way for their
tools to forecast what might happen.
So you can see some sort of potential
threats or potential system issues that
might be going on. This way you got a
little bit more proactive approach to
understanding your incident management
techniques.
One that I think we're probably all
familiar if we've played with chat GPT
or the any of the other popular tools
out there is the natural language query
processing. Being able to intuitively
query
systems and and get information is just
through natural language being able to
talk to it as just though it's another
person has really sped up I think a lot
of people's understanding of how to get
information out of their system which is
really at the heart of observability
as we know.
Automated incident correlation is
another area that we're seeing
capabilities pop up where there's AI
systems now that are helping group
related incidents being able to make it
a little bit more efficient when you go
into start troubleshooting and
debugging.
Business impact analysis is another area
that we've also seen these tools start
to provide some capabilities where some
kind of automated assessment is actually
happening to help us understand how the
system
and the issues that may be happening are
actually affecting our overall business
operations or the goals of the business.
Data Dog actually has something called
RUM, which helps you understand the
business impact of of RUM and using some
AI-enabled stuff in there as well.
Security threat detection is another
area that we are seeing some
capabilities in where we see enhanced
log parsing
and understanding, you know, some of the
using machine learning, I should say,
understanding some of the tools to help
us identify and address security
vulnerabilities before, you know, before
we're
exposed.
And then the next one I've got here is
log analysis. I think
a lot of the vendors, many of the
vendors anyway, are providing some sort
of AI-enabled log analysis to help us
parse through that data and understand
it a little bit better looking for
patterns,
looking for ways to just speed up the
resolution process in general.
Incident clustering and intelligence.
This is a feature that you see out there
across some of them where they're able
to group incidents together and provide
some kind of insight into what's
actually happening with our systems,
what do these incidents mean, you know,
gather grouping them together to show
off that kind of those kinds of
insights.
The next one I got on our list here is
behavioral analysis.
What you'll see here in some of the
vendors is that they're actually using
automated assessment of our system
behavior to help improve the reliability
and and hopefully reduce the downtime
that that is going to inevitably occur
at some point.
Virtual agents and predictive tools is
another one where we've got these
AI-driven agents
that are helpful for incident
prevention. They're also help helpful
for just, you know, operational
enhancements. A lot of a lot of people
are really talking about virtual agents
as as sort of the next wave of of this
movement where you have not just AI
assistants, but you actually have AI
agents out there where they're actually
taking more of a proactive stance and
going out and doing things for you.
Trying to be a little bit more
predictive.
And then the last one in our last our
list here is proactive alerts. I think a
lot of
you know, many of the vendors I should
say are looking for ways to analyze the
data and then look for patterns to help
predict what's going on, finding matches
that allow us to proactively alert the
right people before things either get
worse or or go bad in the first place.
So these these 12
we'll call them capabilities are how I
would sum up all of those vendors that
we looked at in the magic quadrant. If
you looked at all of them said, "Well,
what are all of them doing?" These are
the at a very high level the 12 areas.
But if we were to summarize those into
into a couple into a few things that I
think are really the most important to
probably us
on this call or at least the ones that
I'm seeing the most prevalent. So what
more of a trend is in the incident
management space. And I don't think
anybody's all that surprised by that. A
lot of the things that we use
observability tools is of course part of
an incident management process.
The other one is in the predictive
capabilities. I pointed out some of
those capabilities that we were talking
about. A lot of that is in this vein of
prediction and and and trying to
proactively catch things before they
happen.
And then the last one is in the query
intelligence, which we've talked about
already a lot in terms of the different
chatbots and the agents and stuff like
that being able to use natural language
to inter- interact with these things
that then communicate with our systems
and help us just navigate the data and
the systems in a much more safer way.
But if we go into each of these in a
little bit more detail, you can see that
in the incident management space a lot
of it has to do with that automated RCA
stuff that we talked about, being able
to reduce the resolution time from
probably something like hours or
multiples of minutes to down to seconds
or, you know, few minutes. Those are big
wins for the incident management space.
Being able to
maybe pull in and rank some of the most
likely
parts of the system that are correlating
with the incidents that are happening,
so you can see things that might be
having some downstream effects and then
what those relationships look like. So,
that's a big part of the automated RCA
that I think is a win for a lot of
organizations in this in this category.
The intelligent classification is
another area where
that's helping with incident management
a lot, being able to automatically
categorize issues based on some kind of
predefined criteria. Then also learning
iteratively over time so that, you know,
it can learn from its past incidents and
actually try to improve and refine those
categories moving forward. And then
really one of the interesting things is
as far as like the difference between
humans being involved with this is is
where we can find unbiased
prioritization based on the actual
impact or urgency of situation through
that classification.
Another thing within incident management
is the real-time response automation
that is implemented to help us
really, you know, solve for common
incidents, maybe generate and optimize
resolution scripts, things that are, you
know, things that happen in a more
common way, I guess you could say.
Or maybe executing containment and
mitigation procedures and automating
that initial first response, you know,
like what are the first few things that
a human would do? Let's go ahead and and
make that response part of the
automation in real time and then when
the human arrives on the scene, they'll
have different roles that they'll be
involved with.
And then the last one in the incident
management category that I wanted to
share with you is the advanced analytics
and reporting where we're really talking
about being able to generate a detailed
incident report in real time so that
that when the on-call engineer arrives
into their
channel,
whatever it might be, chat channel, they
can see what's going on. They've got a
nice summary of the incident so far as
it's happened and anything that they
need to know to help go help just dive
in and make a a difference right away,
but also being able to analyze those
incidents
in real time if there are multiple
incidents happening, you can correlate
those together,
find ways to actually predict some of
the things that might
take place in the future incidents and
and try to try to get ahead of those.
And then what I you know, one of the
things that I always have really enjoyed
about some of the stuff I see in this is
in the post incident review, putting
together a lot of the information
that took place with
within our socio-technical system. So
both the the actual, you know, technical
side of the system, but also the human
side and understanding all that together
is part of our learning efforts and and
I think, you know, being able to see all
that generate a lot of that generated
for us can really speed up the process
of learning.
When it comes to the predictive
capabilities, I think the early
detection and prevention is a is a a big
part of what we're seeing here where
the systems, these AI-enabled systems
are helping us to predict and diagnose
those systems before, you know, spotting
these anomalies and and trying to detect
things before they actually go bad and
become critical issues.
Enabling that detection,
you know, can help us ahead of time can
help us actually reduce costs too, and
make sure that the when we do have
disruptions that they they aren't as
costly as they could be.
The next one is our performance
optimization aspect of the predictive
capabilities where we can provide
real-time analytics for tracking the
application performance metrics or maybe
we're monitoring the latency and the
throughput patterns to identify any kind
of potential degradations.
In the security and compliance area,
we've got
you know, systems that are proactively
detecting security vulnerabilities and
threats. We're helping identify
anomalies that could indicate some kind
of data breach and maybe even
automatically detect and map detect and
mask some of the PII information that
might show up in unexpected places.
And then the last one in this group is
cost and efficiency reductions where we
can decrease the incident incident
resolution time hopefully through the
lot of these capabilities which of
course is going to affect our cost, but
we can also optimize data volume through
intelligent filtering and sampling of
that data before we process it and then
of course automating routine monitoring
tasks to help reduce some of that manual
effort is also going to cut cut our
costs in ways.
And then our last group here the natural
language querying we're all probably
familiar with much of this where we can
take you know just normal language you
just talk to the to the models whatever
they may be or the chatbots
in just a normal way you know like you
would to to another person and be able
to query and interact with our systems
in safe ways
just through those natural
conversations. I think that's a lot
those are a lot of great benefits to
help us eliminate the need for
understanding complex query languages or
syntax things like that.
The personalized experience is another
area that I think these natural language
querying aspects are providing some
benefits for us where we can actually
predict the bots or whatever they might
be can predict some of our actions and
help us analyze
you know what it is we we want to do in
terms of our own user behavior and that
way it can optimize the interfaces for
individual users. You know I might get
an interface that's different from the
next person just based on the tasks and
the things that I do.
Smart assistance is another one where
you're seeing
these tools providing context that are
context specific recommendations so that
they can offer a quick explanations on
what to do for certain errors or certain
types of disruptions that you might be
experiencing as well as automating any
kind of routine remediation tasks. I
used to talk a lot about this subject
called ChatOps and I think a lot of this
stuff that we used to talk about ChatOps
is kind of come full circle where we can
now in chat just use common language and
enact or execute commands that happen
throughout our system that can help us
especially in in
you know within the observability space.
And then task simplification kind of
falls into that bucket too where you're
just enabling maybe multiple multi-step
complex multi-step processes and actions
and tasks that can all be automated
so that there's a lot better
coordination really across multiple
services and applications.
So those are the three areas that I
think are really kind of the most
impactful when it comes to the
observability
space and in the AI and LLMs.
I just wanted to point out this one
slide of Datadog here because when you
look at any of these vendors now it's
not just that they have one thing that
falls into the AI LLM enabled space.
They actually have in most cases several
things and you can see here there's a
few things that Datadog offers but the
one thing that I wanted to point out
today
that I think we're super proud of is
that earlier this year there was Datadog
had announced Toto which is a foundation
model for time series forecasting that
we developed in-house and it was trained
on 1 trillion data points and
specifically optimized for observability
use cases. And in all the benchmark
tests Toto demonstrated superior
performance over existing models both in
general purpose forecasting tasks as
well as specifically in the
observability metrics. And another thing
too is that it achieved the
the state of the art you could say
zero-shot performance across multiple
data sets which if you've follow
anything in this AI space anytime you
hear something about uh zero-shot
performance, uh that's always super
impressive.
One more look at some of the main
capabilities that we're seeing in the
space across a lot of different vendors
out there, just to give you an idea and
uh what's going on. But, don't forget
that, you know, when it comes to these
AI and LLM-enabled capabilities of
observability of observability
platforms,
all of it comes down to data. Making
sure that you have really, really great
data, regardless of what it is you're
trying to do, regard- regardless of the
capability that you're drawn to with
this AI and LLM stuff, it's really about
managing that massive amount of data
that we talked about at the beginning of
the session, and understanding that that
data and finding ways to create more
value for users, there's a lot of
answers in that data, and and trying to
um
make sense of it and and sift through it
and do interesting and valuable things
with that, impactful things with it, is
really at the heart of all of this. Um
so, uh
just keep that in mind. And uh as we
start to wrap up here, I've got a few
key takeaways for you for today's
session. I think as we've talked through
a lot of this, I've given you some
general ideas about what a lot of the
vendors are doing when it comes to the
AI and LLMs um out there in the
observability space, and a lot of it
just comes down to data analysis and
having really great advanced automated
ways of of understanding that data,
making sure that we can um instantly
detect anomalies and make our systems a
little bit more efficient and our
monitoring efforts a lot more efficient
through analyzing that data in a number
of ways.
The other takeaway is that generative AI
and LLMs are now, uh you know, enhancing
our monitoring efforts by finding those
those uh patterns, those hidden patterns
that we can't find as humans in all this
complex and vast data. And then the
other one uh the last one here um is how
generative AI and LLMs are now really
improving our system reliability by
reducing some of the manual
troubleshooting and and creating a lot
more intuitive interactions with our
systems and allowing us to
just have a much better overall
performance and experience as we are
interacting with our systems and
troubleshooting and and that kind of
thing and hopefully you know creating a
little bit better modernization
practices within our observability
efforts.
Well, I promised you the link to this
resources again. So here it is.
You can follow the QR code. It'll take
you to the same place, but this is a
like I mentioned earlier I think this is
a GitHub repo. I've got all the links to
everything I talked about today.
Feel free to go download that. You also
have all of the slides and that kind of
stuff.
And with that I think we've got some
time for questions. So I really
appreciate y'all having me out here
today. It's been a pleasure to talk to
you about AI and LLMs in the
observability space. And Deion, what you
got for me?
Hey, thank you so much Jason. So
one of the fun parts of the the
weirdness of these LLMs is when they
kind of surprise you
in different ways whether that's
asking it to write some things and it
comes up with creative things or
creative code or the like. I was curious
if
you have any you've seen through your
customers or like any kind of surprises
where you know, the the LLM's been able
to find things that you know, was kind
of an aha moment for a customer or some
of the other you know, capabilities that
you've talked about where it's just like
that that je ne sais quoi that comes
with the LLM has kind of popped up.
Yeah. Yeah, I think what you're
referring to is
hallucinations one of our favorite uh uh
uh
byproducts I think of a lot of these a
lot of these tools that are out now is
that they're not always um
uh well, like you mentioned at the
beginning they're a black box and they
um
they're unpredictable. You know, they're
not always going to provide the same
results given the same inputs. And so,
yeah, that is a concern. I think it
really depends on, you know, the
application. Of course, there are there
are tools out there. Data Dog is a great
example where we've got something called
the LLM observability tool to allow us
to identify hallucinations and see those
as they come in and go out. We've got
some ways to analyze that data and you
know, again, goes back to the pattern
matching. If we've seen this type of
stuff before, we can see that, you know,
this doesn't match the type of input we
had and the expected output that we were
looking for. So,
I think when it comes to a lot of the
enhancements and and the things that I
was sharing with you,
you know, those are the capabilities a
lot of vendors are are providing and and
it's really on them to try to understand
and make sure that they're capturing
everything they need to know about these
hallucinations and and and keep tabs of
that. But, you bring up a good point. If
you're a business and you've got some AI
or LLMs enabled in your system that's
providing a service for a user, how do
you keep an eye on the output and make
sure that it's providing the right
answers? It is still a a huge challenge
for a lot of folks. Um
and I I think, you know, there are some
vendors out there, Data Dog included,
who do have some solutions to help um
make sense of some of that.
Got it. Sounds good.
Okay. We have a question here. What do
you think LLMs will not be great at in
observability?
Oh, wow, that is a good one. You know, I
in my experimenting with different LLMs,
it is good for
writing up, you know, copywriting type
of things. And I think we're seeing in
post-incident reviews and in incident
summaries, it's giving us a lot of good
data there and and and writing that kind
of stuff up. But, I think if you try to
allow LLMs or AI to write too much,
um it it seems to stumble on at that
point. And I don't know if that's just
some of the tools that I've experimented
with so far, but I I feel like I in my
mind, summarizing transcripts and and
things like that, um these tools are
great at that kind of thing. But if you
if you want them to come up with
something creatively, and you don't have
a really solid rag system or someplace
for it to go extract that data from, and
it just has to rely on its own uh
pre-built models, it it doesn't do as
well in those cases. So, I think you
have to limit how much it's creating for
you, or at least in limit it in sort of
smaller sizes, so that um it's not just
trying to write you huge large volumes
of information, and then it'll get lost
in the in the plot, I think. Usually is
what I my experience is, anyway.
Got it. And then, certain LLMs seem to
be particularly good at, you know,
certain things. So, like Sonnet 3.5
has a good vibe check for me when it
writes code. It feels like it's the kind
of code that I prefer compared to other
models. Have you noticed similar things
in the uh with the type of task that
you've been talking about, where like a
certain model may be better for one
task, and maybe another one for another
task?
You know, so far I have not been able to
identify anything like that in my own
experimentation. Now, I will be honest,
I have not gone through all of the
vendors and tried out all of their
tools. Uh I can only kind of speak to
the things with within DataDog and some
of the things I've experimented with,
like you're talking about with Sonnet
and Claude and ChatGPT. And um I I I
don't know that I have a favorite. I
feel like ChatGPT has been pretty good
to me early on, but it's a little less
valuable to me lately. Uh I've done some
interesting things with Google Vertex
and and had some success over there with
Gemini. Um but I I don't have, at least
right now, a mental model on which ones
are best suited for certain things.
But that is something I've actually
recently tried to tried to make an
effort to understand because now it's
it's not just that there's a couple of
different models.
All of the vendors have multiples of
models and just understanding, you know,
just the ones of of let's say ChatGPT
use
what's the use case scenario for every
one of them and understanding that is a
is becoming a bigger task than it used
to be.
Yeah, it makes sense. Well, thanks so
much Jason. Really appreciate it. Thanks
for taking the time.
Yeah, thanks you and appreciate it and
yeah, we'll see you sometime soon.
Sounds good. Cheers.